Problem Solver. Quick Learner. Firefighter.

I'm a self-motivated, tech enthusiast with good communication skills, I look forward to learn new technologies and set a mark in the market. I currently have a good understanding of Full Stack Web development with Reactjs, Nextjs, Bootstrap & Tailwind CSS, SASS, Angular, Asp.NET Core 3.x, WebAPI and have worked with Google Maps api, Third party Login Integration with Firebase, Machine Learning, CMS e.g. Wordpress, Shopify, WooCommerce, etc.

Resume Online: https://chkashifjaved.github.io

Professional Experience / 3 Years

ASSOSIATE SOFTWARE ENGINEER (NEXTJS, .NET CORE) / MARCHE TECH STUDIO INC - Lahore, Pakistan

May 2021 - Present

themarche.ca, bazaarr.pk (Nextjs projects on which I developed components, and worked)

- Frontend: Nextjs
- Backend: Asp.NET Core

These both products have private UMS and ComplianceWeb Consoles. ComplianceWeb project is developed by me, and UMS by my seniors.

ComplianceWeb:

- Frontend: Bootstrap, Javascript, jQuery, Datatables.
- Backend: Asp.NET Core, EF Core (lambda queries), and consumed their other private APIs.

FULL STACK DEVELOPER & ML PROGRAMMER / MEDRUUM HEALTH SERVICES (PRIVATE) LIMITED - Lahore, Pakistan

Apr 2020 - Jan 2021

Bahmni (MRS), a medical record open-source system.

- Frontend: Bootstrap, Angular, SASS
- Backend: Custom Framework (Core PHP)
- ML: Python, Tensorflow, Transfer Learning (I was working n researching on health e.g. lung cancer, heart issues, chest cancer, maleria .etc. issues to be detected by machine using Al and machine learning n deep learning).

Patient-Nurse Matching System:

- Frontend: Bootstrap
- Backend: Custom Framework (Core PHP)

JUNIOR DEVELOPER (LARAVEL) / BLUEHORN TECHNOLOGIES - Lahore, Pakistan

Jan 2019 - Dec 2019

Food Delivery App: US client project, developed from scratch with Merchant Panel and stripe payment gateway integration.

- Frontend: Bootstrap
- Backend: Laravel

Education

UET SCOCS / Bachelors , Information Technology (2020) / 3.4 CGPA

(Lahore)

Garrison Boys Intermediate College and High School / Intermediate/A-Level , Computer Science (2016) / 86%

(Lahore)

St. Stephen High School / Matriculation/O-Level , Computer Science (2014) / 80%

(Lahore)

Certifications

Natural Language Processing in Tensorflow

Starting Apr 2020

Coursera & Deeplearning.ai

coursera.org/verify/N3MXWQ7B5BAD

Machine Learning - Fundamentals

Starting Apr 2020

Youaccel

Intro to Tensorflow for AI, ML and DL

Starting Apr 2020

Coursera & Deeplearning.ai

coursera.org/verify/3R7SC28XL6HU

Web Scraping and API Fundamentals in Python

Starting Apr 2020

365 Datascience

Arduino using Blocky (Google Blocks)

Starting Sep 2019



Udemy ude.my/UC-14SGACV3 DS & ML Fundamentals Starting Aug 2019 ude.my/UC-H5NA2IDN UET iTec19 - IT Quiz Competition Starting Mar 2019 University of Engineering and Technology, Lahore **Skills** ■■■■ AJAX ■■■■ Angular ■■■■ Asp.NET Core ■ ■ ■ ■ Bootstrap --- C# **CSS 3** ■■■■ JavaScript ■■■■ EF Core ■■■■ HTML 5 Laravel ■■■■ Nextjs --- OOP ■■■■ PHP ■■■ Python ■ ■ ■ ■ React SASS SQL ■■■■ TailwindCSS ■ ■ ■ ■ Tensorflow ■ ■ ■ ■ TypeScript **Projects** Learning Management System / Semester Project Tools: HTML, CSS, JS, Bootstrap, PHP, OOP, MySQLi Smart Display Monitoring System / Final Year Project Tools: Machine Learning, Deep Learning, Python, Tensorflow, Keras Monitor displayed products smartly using ML and DL. Console App - Payroll Management System / OOP & File Handling, Semeter Project Tools: C++, OOP, File Handling Chrome Extention (Bulk Image Downloader) / Harward CS50 Project Tools: Javascript, Chrome APIs **Awards** IT Quiz Competition Runner | UET iTec19, 2019

Functional Areas	Industries
Researcher	Information Technology
Software & Web Development	
Languages	Hobbies
Languages Urdu - Native	Hobbies ML Articles Reading